<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Renormalized</title>
  <subtitle>Thinking and talking about normal things, just differently</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-10-03T22:15:53.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>cheshyre</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Lifting Log: Oct 3, 2016</title>
    <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/26/lifting-log-oct-3-2016/"/>
    <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/26/lifting-log-oct-3-2016/</id>
    <published>2016-09-26T22:34:41.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-10-03T22:15:53.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week was fine with one glaring exception. I attend The Ohio State University and I use the facilities available to students to work out. I also live far off campus and either take the bus or drive to campus, and on Saturdays (when I usually buy my groceries) I drive to campus. Another thing that happens on Saturdays is college football, and this week the game happened to be early enough that even though I left for campus at nine I was unable to find any parking available to students. It appears that OSU also closed off a couple extra lots that are normally dedicated to student permit parking during games. So basically I could not park on campus and as a result was unable to work out or study in the library later. Sometimes I wonder exactly why I hate the big three American sports (football, basketball, baseball), but this weekend I clearly remembered why. It’s no longer something as simple as an interest for fans; it is truly something similar to a religion, causing its followers to disregard all others in the pursuit of their fanaticism. I’m acting very bitter, but as someone looking from the outside in, I can understand their behavior even less than the behavior of the people I know that are very religious.</p>
<p>Today (Oct 3), I failed on my last overhead press rep (which was unfortunate). I also failed to complete more chinup reps than last time, but considering the circumstances, I am pretty satisfied. I am also growing more and more content with the development of my body, only really being upset at my inability to eat enough to put on weight in any consistent manner. I need to adjust my diet to include more variety, but I also just need to figure out how I can eat more while keeping my food fairly healthy. I also need to eat more vegetables (I don’t think I’ve eaten any in 2 or 3 weeks).</p>
<p>Body weight: 138 lbs (measured after working out at 4pm so probably a couple pounds heavier than normal)<br>Primary goal for next week: eat more, progress on chinups</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;This week was fine with one glaring exception. I attend The Ohio State University and I use the facilities available to students to work 
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Lifting Log: Sept 26, 2016</title>
    <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/06/lifting-log-sept-26-2016/"/>
    <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/06/lifting-log-sept-26-2016/</id>
    <published>2016-09-06T18:22:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-09-26T22:34:41.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So this is my attempt at giving myself some impetus to post more consistently. I’m going to try to document the progress I see at the end of each week of lifting, which for me is on Monday since I do my workouts on Thursday, Saturday, and Monday.</p>
<p>After a week and a half of being too sick to go to the gym, I went back. Unfortunately, my inactivity put me in a position where I had to deload 10%, even after having to deload just before getting sick. So currently my squat is at 140 lbs, my squat is at 155 lbs, and my bench is at 95 lbs. However, I feel pretty good after this week of working out, and I am ready to progress to weighted dips (getting to weighted chin-ups will probably take another week or two).</p>
<p>Body weight: 135 lbs<br>Long-term goals: gain weight, move towards two-plate world for squats, one-plate world for bench</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;So this is my attempt at giving myself some impetus to post more consistently. I’m going to try to document the progress I see at the end
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Time For A New Blog</title>
    <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/01/time-for-a-new-blog/"/>
    <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/01/time-for-a-new-blog/</id>
    <published>2016-09-02T02:27:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-09-06T18:22:08.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome everyone to the new and reimagined blog. I am trying a couple things differently now. First, I am using Hexo to generate my blog locally, rather than having Jekyll build it after committing to the repo. This has a couple benefits: first, Jekyll (or specifically Liquid) is annoying to deal with; second, I can test things easily without putting changes into production, allowing me to avoid millions of embarrassing commits; third, I can probably make a better structured site like this.</p>
<p>For the time being, things will probably continue as normal. I will post on the current theme about anime, sports, school, physics, and other things while working on a new theme that I will write from scratch. This will be the challenge for this iteration of the site, as figuring out exactly what a Hexo theme needs to do, and also what it is capable of, will take some time. Fortunately, between testing, I can just switch themes and everything will work fine, so I won’t be motivated to neglect my writing with the rationalization that changing the aesthetic of the website should change the structure (which was true while I was working with Jekyll).</p>
<p>I have a couple ideas for the site in the future (in no particular order):</p>
<ul>
<li>I will not bring back the guides or HLTB section (at least as they were) because it felt like they were mostly empty and I did not have enough to say on most things to make those worth it.</li>
<li>I will work to do a good job of tagging most of the things I write, so that some form of categories can be used to get indexes of similar posts.</li>
<li>I will write a page detailing my current setups.</li>
<li>I will write a “future” post detailing short-term and long-term interests/goals that should serve as a reminder to me to get things done and also allow people who actually care to follow along.</li>
</ul>
<p>That should cover basically everything an intro post should cover.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Welcome everyone to the new and reimagined blog. I am trying a couple things differently now. First, I am using Hexo to generate my blog 
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
