<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Renormalized</title>
  <subtitle>Thinking and talking about normal things, just differently</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-09-02T03:25:49.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>cheshyre</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Time For A New Blog</title>
    <link href="https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/01/time-for-a-new-blog/"/>
    <id>https://cheshyre.github.io/2016/09/01/time-for-a-new-blog/</id>
    <published>2016-09-02T02:27:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-09-02T03:25:49.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome everyone to the new and reimagined blog. I am trying a couple things differently now. First, I am using Hexo to generate my blog locally, rather than having Jekyll build it after committing to the repo. This has a couple benefits: first, Jekyll (or specifically Liquid) is annoying to deal with; second, I can test things easily without putting chnages into production, allowing me to avoid millions of embarrassing commits; third, I can probably make a better structured site like this.</p>
<p>For the time being, things will probably continue as normal. I will post on the current theme about anime, sports, school, physics, and other things while working on a new theme that I will write from scratch. This will be the challenge for this iteration of the site, as figuring out exactly what a Hexo theme needs to do, and also what it is capable of, will take some time. Fortunately, between testing, I can just switch themes and everything will work fine, so I won’t be motivated to neglect my writing with the rationalization that changing the aesthetic of the website should change the structure (which was true while I was working with Jekyll).</p>
<p>I have a couple ideas for the site in the future (in no particular order):<br>~</p>
<ul>
<li>I will not bring back the guides or HLTB section (at least as they were) because it felt like they were mostly empty and I did not have enough to say on most things to make those worth it</li>
<li>I will work to do a good job of tagging most of the things I write, so that some form of categories can be used to get indexes of similar posts.</li>
<li>I will write a page detailing my current setups.</li>
<li>I will write a “future” post detailing short-term and long-term interests/goals that should serve as a reminder to me to get things done and also allow people who actually care to follow along.</li>
</ul>
<p>That should cover basically everything an intro post should cover.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Welcome everyone to the new and reimagined blog. I am trying a couple things differently now. First, I am using Hexo to generate my blog 
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
